<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' standalone='yes'?>


<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE ... YOU WILL LOSE YOUR WORK -->


<c74object name='link.beat' category='link,  time,  timing'>

	<digest>Synchronize beats with a Link timeline</digest>
	<description>Synchronize beats with a Link timeline. Ableton Link ia a technology that synchronizes musical beat, tempo, and phase across multiple applications running on one or more devices. <br/>
<br/>
Ableton Link is licensed for use within Max.If you would like to incorporate Link support into a Max standalone application, it will require a specific license for your application.If you are a standalone developer interested in including Link support, please contact Ableton at link-devs@ableton.com for more license related information.For more technical information on Link, please visit https://ableton.github.io/link/. </description>


	<!--METADATA-->

	<metadatalist>
		<metadata name='author'>Cycling '74 </metadata>
		<metadata name='tag'>link</metadata>
		<metadata name='tag'>time</metadata>
		<metadata name='tag'>timing</metadata>
	</metadatalist>


	<!--ARGUMENTS-->

	<objarglist>

	</objarglist>


	<!--MESSAGES-->

	<methodlist>

		<method name='int'>
			<digest>Turn on/off the output of beats</digest>
			<description>Turn on/off the output of beats. Beats will be output at the specified <at>tempo</at> and phase aligned with the Link timeline. </description>
		</method>

	</methodlist>


	<!--ATTRIBUTES-->

	<attributelist>

		<attribute name='granularity' get='1' set='1' type='float64' size='1' >
			<digest>Granularity of scheduling for subdivisions</digest>
			<description>Granularity of scheduling for subdivisions. Lower values will increase accuracy, higher values will increase efficiency. </description>
		</attribute>

		<attribute name='peers' get='1' set='0' type='long' size='1' >
			<digest>Number of participants in the Link session</digest>
			<description>Number of participants in the Link session. </description>
		</attribute>

		<attribute name='subdivisions' get='1' set='1' type='float64' size='1' >
			<digest>Number of subdivisions per beat</digest>
			<description>Number of subdivisions per beat. This determines the rate of bangs at the third outlet. </description>
		</attribute>

		<attribute name='quantum' get='1' set='1' type='float64' size='1' >
			<digest>The number of beats in a group</digest>
			<description>The number of beats in a group. Quantum could be thought of as the number of beats in a bar or measure. However, quantum could be any arbitrary number of beats and is not linked directly to a host or timeline. Integer numbers will work best for quantum, thought decimal values are also permitted. </description>
		</attribute>

		<attribute name='tempo' get='1' set='1' type='float64' size='1' >
			<digest>Tempo in beats per minute</digest>
			<description>Tempo in beats per minute. Setting the tempo will set it for all participants in the Link timeline. </description>
		</attribute>

	</attributelist>


	<!--RELATED-->

	<seealsolist>
		<seealso name='link.phasor~' />
		<seealso name='metro' />
		<seealso name='tempo' />
	</seealsolist>


</c74object>
